export default  [
{
	"question": "Wat is de antwoord van 2x6= ?",
	"option1" : "3",
	"option2": "4",
	"option3": "8",
	"option4": "12",
	"answer": 4
},
{
	"question": "De som van 2 en 3",
	"option1" : "2",
	"option2": "5",
	"option3": "7",
	"option4": "9",
	"answer": 2
},
{
	"question": "welke antwoord is 8",
	"option1" : "1+3x2=",
	"option2": "16:2=",
	"option3": "3x3-3=",
	"option4": "9+1=",
	"answer": 2
},
{
	"question": "welke antwoord is niet gelijk dan 8?",
	"option1": "2x2+4=",
	"option2": "4x4:2=",
	"option3": "3X3+1=",
	"option4": "2+2+2+2=",
	"answer": 3
}, 
{
	"question": "Symbol voor plus",
	"option1": "*",
	"option2": "+",
	"option3": "$",
	"option4": "#",
	"answer": 2
}, 
{
	"question": "5x2=",
	"option1": "10",
	"option2": "5",
	"option3": "15",
	"option4": "20",
	"answer": 1
}, 
{
	"question": "4x8+2=?",
	"option1": "30",
	"option2": "40",
	"option3": "34",
	"option4": "28",
	"answer": 3
}, 
{
	"question": "50x0=?",
	"option1": "0",
	"option2": "50",
	"option3": "25",
	"option4": "1",
	"answer": 1
}, 
{
	"question": "1+1=?",
	"option1": "0",
	"option2": "4",
	"option3": "1",
	"option4": "2",
	"answer": 4
}, 
{
	"question": "50:0=? ",
	"option1": "50",
	"option2": "0",
	"option3": "1",
	"option4": "Kan niet",
	"answer": 4
}		
]